Alexandra Hionis

alexandra.hionis@gmail.com | (610)-329-4279 | West Chester, PA 19382

 $Linked In: \underline{https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexandra-hionis-she-her-4940071b5/\ |\ Github: \underline{https://github.com/Alexandra-Hionis-she-her-4940071b5/\ |\ Github: \underline{https://github.com/Al$

Portfolio: https://alexandra-hionis.github.io/

SUMMARY

Full stack web developer and recent graduate of Penn LPS coding bootcamp with the ability to design and build web applications from the ground up. I have achieved the technical skills and knowledge that are needed to succeed as a web developer and I am looking forward to working with more experienced developers and to continuously grow in the tech industry. My background in psychology and business, infused with my creativity, attention to detail, and problem-solving skills allow for me to consistently deliver positive results and solve complex problems for my clients and teammates.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, ¡Query, Bootstrap, FireBase, Node.js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handlebars, React

PROJECTS

UMEWE | https://github.com/oxfordblucher/Restaurant-Roulette | https://oxfordblucher.github.io/Restaurant-Roulette/

- Finds a restaurant location between two addresses for two people to meet
- Languages: HTML, Bootstrap & CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax

Daily Planner | https://github.com/Alexandra-Hionis/Daily-Work-Planner | https://alexandra-hionis.github.io/Daily-Work-Planner/

- Saves a user's hourly to-dos with an hourly-responsive format
- Languages: HTML, Bootstrap & CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

JavaScript Quiz | https://github.com/Alexandra-Hionis/JavaScript-Quiz | https://alexandra-hionis.github.io/JavaScript-Quiz/

- Timed JavaScript quiz with multiple-choice questions
- Languages: HTML, Bootstrap & CSS, JavaScript

EXPERIENCE

Mendenhall Inn | Mendenhall, PA

Accounting Clerk

May 2017 – March 2020

- Communicated with CPA in a professional manner, resolved uncertain entries by providing documentary support
- Demonstrated team success working with the sales team to create invoices for private parties and weddings

Center City Crime Victim Services | Philadelphia, PA

Psychology Intern

October 2016 – December 2016

- Successfully entered and organized data entries of victim information
- Provided support to victims while attending preliminary hearings at Philadelphia's City Hall

PRESENTATIONS

• "Diagnosing Celebrities: From Poetic Madness to Personality Disorder" presented at Temple University's Undergraduate Research Forum and Creative Works Symposium, 2014

ACTIVITIES & AWARDS

- Psychology Majors Association at Temple University
- National Society of Collegiate Scholars Member
- Volunteer for the Hellenic News of America, Hermes Expo International
- Alvernia University's Community Outreach Partnership Scholarship Recipient, 2011-2012

EDUCATION

PENN LPS CODING BOOTCAMP | University of Pennsylvania & Trilogy Education Bootcamp Certificate

February 2021

TEMPLE UNIVERSITY | College of Liberal Arts | Philadelphia, PA *Bachelor of Arts (B.A.):* Psychology | *Minor:* Business Administration